fruitshootusa.com 2017-05-24

# Privacy Policy

While we think having fun is serious business, we're also serious about your privacy. 

Here's how we treat the personal information we collect through this website. 

### Your Privacy

We at Britvic take the privacy of your personal information seriously. The following explains how we treat personal information collected through this website.

### Information for children under 13

If you are under 13 years old, it is very important that your parent/guardian has given you permission to use this website. We take measures to prevent children under 13 from posting or publicly disclosing their personally identifiable information on or through this site. 

### Details we collect

Our website collects certain technical information, such as your IP address, browser type and operating system. We do not collect personal information, such as full name, e-mail address, home address or telephone number without the permission of a parent or guardian, unless we are expressly authorized to do so by law. Where we do collect personal information with permission, we do not collect more information than needed for participating in the on-line activities. 

### How we use your details

If we ask you to provide information that may identify you, our request will be specific. If we ask you to provide additional information, we will explain why we need it and how it will be used. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us. Our database is held securely and any information you submit may be used in the following ways: 

  * To better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services;
  * To study the behaviour of visitors to our site;

### Disclosing your details

If we need to pass your details to our suppliers and other people we engage in running our business, we will require them to keep it confidential for this purpose. Like most organisations, Britvic's web server automatically collects and aggregates information about your visit including, but not limited to, your IP address, service provider, browser type and operating system. This information is anonymized so as not to personally identify you and we analyse this aggregated information only in order to optimise your experience and enhance the time spent with us online, and we maintain it in a manner so that we are not able to re-identify you. 

### Cookies and website data

On visiting the site, Britvic may store information in the form of a cookie on your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data sent by a website's server to your computer or mobile device and stored in your browser. Cookies are intended to improve your user experience by making it easier and faster to navigate through a website. This allows us to track your usage of the site, although we will not monitor your use of individual pages. You can block cookies, erase them once they have been stored, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. It is important to note that you will lose some functions of a website if you choose to restrict or disable its cookies. Please refer to your internet browser's Help section for more information. 

### Sending information abroad

This site is hosted and maintained by Britvic Soft Drinks Limited a company registered in England and Wales with its registered offices at Britvic head office, Breakspear Park, Breakspear Way, Hemel Hempstead, HP2 4TZ. Britvic will cause Britvic Soft Drinks Limited to comply with the terms of this policy. 

### Policy changes

From time to time, we may make changes to this policy. Britvic North America LLC is a Florida corporation with offices located at 220 N. Westshore Blvd, Suite 200, Tampa, FL 33607. Britvic Soft Drinks Limited is a company registered in England and Wales with its registered offices at Britvic head office, Breakspear Park, Breakspear Way, Hemel Hempstead, HP2 4TZ. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact Britvic Digital team by sending an e-mail to [privacy@britvicdigital.co.uk](mailto:privacy@britvicdigital.co.uk) with the word Unsubscribe in the subject.
